-You know Mom hates when I'm late. -I told you...
-你知道的，妈妈讨厌我迟到 -我告诉过你...
we should have left earlier. It's the same damn thing every year.
我们应该早点走的 每年都一样的该死
It's always: "Where are my blue shoes, dear?"
总是：“亲爱的， 我蓝色的鞋子在哪？“
Or: "Dad, I can't find my Marilyn Bronson CD."
或是：“爸爸，我找不到 玛莲布朗森的CD。”
-Marilyn Manson. -Whatever her name is.
-玛莲曼森 -我才不管她的名字是什么
-She's a guy, dad. -Marilyn? A guy?
-她是男的，爸爸 -玛莲？男的？
What's the world coming to?
-这世界怎么了？
-Oh, boy... -Are you all right, darling?
- 哦，男孩... -没什么吧，亲爱的？
Yeah.
耶
Dad! Dad!
爸爸！爸爸！
Oh, God!
哦，上帝！
My God, what happened?
上帝啊，发生什么了？
-Are we there yet? -ls anybody hurt?
-我们在那吗？ -由人受伤吗？
-Marion, are you okay? -Are you crazy?
-玛丽恩，你没事吧？ -你疯了吗？
-You almost killed us! -I'm sorry. I must have dozed off.
-你差点杀了我们！ -对不起，我一定是打瞌睡了
I hope you slept well. Maybe I should whip you up some breakfast.
我希望你睡好了. 也许我该更快的为你准备早餐.
Nobody is hurt. Get off my back, all right?
没人受伤 别唠叨了, 行吗?
For Pete's sakes, why don't you let someone else drive, for once?
看在上帝的份上, 为什么你不能让其他人开车哪, 就一次?
Don't worry. That woke me up.
不用担心 我已经醒了
The pie is probably ruined.
这个派可能已经毁了
-Oh, Jesus! -What is that?
-哦，上帝啊！ -那是什么？
-It's pumpkin and chocolate. -Smells like ass.
-南瓜和巧克力 -闻起来象是大便
I'd better go out and check the car.
我最好出去检查一下车子
The son of a bitch didn't even stop!
妈的还没停下!
-Where are we? -We're on the road.
-我们在哪？ -我们在路上
-What does it look like? -What happened to the lnterstate?
-这看起来象是什么？ --大路上有什么事?
I thought we could take the back-way for a change.
我认为我们应该掉头
What's wrong with the lnterstate? We've taken it for years!
大路怎么了？ 我们几年来一直都从那走
I was bored.
我听够了
And I didn't wanna... fall asleep.
我不想...睡着了
-That seemed to work. -All right.
-好像有用 -好的
Car looks okay. No damage.
车子看起来没问题了 没有损伤
-Want me to take the wheel, dad? -No, thank you, dear.
-要我拿轮子吗，爸爸？ -不，谢谢，亲爱的
-I'm growing attached to this car. -Here we go again.
-我和这车子一起长大. -又是这样.
Did you or did you not put the Mercedes in the junkyard?
你以前有没有把梅塞德斯扔在废车场过？
-lt wasn't my fault! -I'm just teasing you, sweetheart.
-不是我的错！ -只是个玩笑，甜心
There certainly aren't very many people on this road.
没多少人在这路上
It's Christmas Eve. Most people are at home, with their families.
圣诞节前夜。大多数人在家里， 和家人一起
-Damn, I'm starving! -Me too.
- 该死，我饿死了 -我也是
I hope your mother doesn't get experimental with that turkey.
我希望你妈不是拿火鸡做实验
Look, can we drop the subject? I don't feel very good.
我们不能放弃这个话题吗？ 我觉得不舒服
Are you okay, honey-bunny? You want us to stop?
你还好吧，宝贝？ 你想我们停下？
Long car rides make me queasy. And all this talk food isn't helping any.
长途旅程让我心慌 谈论食物也没什么用处
-How about a couple of bookers? -Shut up, Richard!
- 订餐怎么样？ -闭嘴，理查德
-Or some Macaroni and dick-cheese. -Richard, that's disgusting!
-或者通心面和鸭酱 -理查德，那很恶心
But, mom, there really is a cheese called dick-cheese. Chinese make it.
- 但是，妈妈，确实有一种奶酪叫 鸭酱，中国人发明的
You've had dick-cheese before, right, Brad?
你以前吃过鸭酱，是吧，布莱德
-Grow up, Richard. -It's 7:30 already, darling.
- 成熟点，理查德 -已经7点半了，亲爱的
I'm aware of that, Laura. I thought we'd come to a junction by now.
我注意到了，劳拉。 我想我们现在在一个交叉口上
Jesus, Laura, do you have to suck on it like that?
上帝，劳拉，你非要那样喝吗？
-That's the way I drink. -All right, you guys. Calm down.
- 那是我喝东西的方式 -好了，冷静下来
-Take it easy. -Marion is right.
-放松 -玛丽恩是对的
When I played baseball, they taught us this technique to help us relax.
当我打棒球的时候 他们教我们这种方法来放松
I still use it sometimes.
有的时候我仍然在用
You breathe in deeply through your nose and out through your mouth.
用鼻子深吸一口气 用嘴呼出
Thank you, Brad.
谢谢，布莱德
-Can I ask you a question, though? -Sure.
- 我能问你个问题吗？ -当然
Was your entire school gay, or was it just the baseball team?
你整个学校都是同性恋， 还是只是棒球队是
-Richard! -What?
- 理查德！ -什么？
Richard, it's a technique we use to helps us get in what we call...
理查德，这是个技巧 用来帮助我们进入一种我们称之为...
..."The Zone". -The Homo Zone?
...“地带” -同志地带？
Richard!
-理查德！
This is such a beautiful night!
多么美丽的夜晚啊！
Does anybody know the name of that really bright star right in front of us?
谁知道我们正前面那颗闪亮的星星 的名字吗？
There's 1 50 billion stars up there, for Christ's sake.
那有1亿5千万颗星星， 看在上帝的份上
That one I know. That bright one is the North Star. The only one I know.
那颗我知道。很亮的那颗是北极星 我唯一知道的一颗
Thank you.
谢谢
-Let's sing a song, everybody. -Okay. What?
- 唱首歌吧 -好的。唱什么？
-How about "Yellow Submarine"? -We always do that one.
- “黄色潜水艇”怎么样？ -我们总唱那首
-Brad, how about "Y.M.C.A"? -It's Christmas, so how about...
- 布莱德，“Y.M.C.A”怎么样？ -今天圣诞节，那么...
"Jingle Bells"?
- “铃儿响叮当”？
Come on. Come on.
拜托。拜托
You like that part, don't you?
你喜欢那部分，不是吗？
Why did you stop?
你为什么停下？
A woman. I saw a woman in the forest.
一个女人 我看到森林里有个女人
-Cool. Dad is tripping out. -Richard.
-酷。爸爸发昏了 -理查德
-Are you sure, dad? -Well, yeah.
- 你确定吗，爸爸？ -嗯，是的
Dressed in white. She was holding something.
穿着白色衣服。 抱着什么东西
Fuck!
操！
Hi there.
嗨
We are a little lost.
我们有点迷路了
You wouldn't happen to know the quickest way back to the highway?
你知不知道最快回到高速公路的路线？
Are you all right?
你没事吧？
Did you have an accident or something?
你有意外还是什么？
Okay. Anybody got a cell phone?
好吧，谁有手机？
-No signal. -We just passed the cabin.
- 没有信号。 -我们刚刚经过小木屋
Maybe there's a phone. Richard, be a gentleman and make room for her.
也许那里有电话。理查德， 绅士一点，给她腾点地方
-Let Brad be the gentleman. -What's your problem, man?
- 让布莱德做绅士吧 -你怎么了？
Relax, buddy.
- 放松，兄弟
Breath in slowly through your nose and out deeply through your ass!
通过你的鼻子慢慢吸气 通过你的屁眼放出来
-It's all right, Mrs. Harrington. -I'll walk.
- 没事，哈灵顿太太 -我走着好了
-I could use the fresh air, anyway. -You're not walking by yourself.
-我还可以呼吸新鲜空气 -你不能一个人走
-I wanna be alone. -Marion!
- 我希望一个人 -玛丽恩！
-Let me tell you something, smart guy. -What?
-告诉你，聪明的家伙 -什么？
Keep busting my balls and I'll take you out of the game for good.
再触我霉头我就踢你出局
-Understand me? -Yes, sir!
- 明白吗？ -是的，长官！
We'll meet you down there in just a minute. Okay, honey?
一分钟后我们会在那里遇到你 好吗？
Okay.
好的
All right.
好吧
Okay, we'll see you there, honey.
好的，到那再见，亲爱的
Shit!
-操！
Would you like a nice hot cup of coffee?
想要一杯美妙的热咖啡吗？
I think she's in shock. We should have asked Marion what to do.
我想她吓坏了 我们应该问问玛丽恩
Honey, we don't need a shrink. We'll call 91 1.
亲爱的，我们不需要害怕 打电话给911
-Okay. -They'll know how to handle it.
-好的 -他们知道如何处理
Damn! Fucking stinks in here.
操！这里他妈的臭死了
It's the baby...
是孩子...
jack-ass.
妈的
-Where are you going, sweetie? -Away from you guys.
-你去哪，宝贝？ -离开你们这些家伙
Teenagers.
毛孩子
What's your name?
你叫什么？
Where do you live?
你住在哪？
-She's not gonna be much help. -No.
- 她没什么用 - 不
Hello, Miss July.
你好，七月小姐
Does anybody live here?
有人住在这里吗？
Maybe it's one of those old forest ranger stations.
这可能是护林员的临时住所
Jesus, Laura. You scared the shit out of me.
上帝啊，劳拉 你吓死我了
Sorry. They have very interesting wall hangings, these rangers.
对不起。 这些护林员的装饰品很有趣
So, what's his name?
那么，他叫什么？
Do it, baby.
做吧，宝贝
You got a ring. You married?
你戴着戒指，你结婚了？
Marion and I are getting married.
玛丽恩和我快结婚了
Actually...
事实上...
don't say anything but I'm proposing to her tonight at her grandmother's.
不要说出来 我准备今晚在她祖母家向她求婚
Remember when you said you would kill yourself if I ever left you?
还记得你说过如果我离开你 你就会自杀？
I hope that was just a figure of speech, 'cause...
我希望那只是一种表达方式 因为...
Brad, we've had some great times together, but...
布莱德，我们曾有过美好时光 但是...
I think we need to go on with our lives separately.
我认为我们需要分开了
Shit.
操
-Damn! -Was there no dial tone?
- 该死 - 没有拨号音？
Nao, Laura, I just forgot the number for 91 1.
不，劳拉，我忘了911的号码
It's Amy.
这是艾米
My little girl. Her name is Amy.
我的小女儿 她叫艾米
-She's so cold. -Not surprised. It's freezing here.
- 她好冷 -不稀奇，这里冷死了
-You hold her. -No.
-你抱着她 -不
I'm not really a baby kind of guy.
我不是能照顾孩子的人
How does she breathe with all those blanket on her face?
那么多毯子在她脸上 她怎么呼吸啊？
Don't worry.
不用担心
She's dead.
她死了
That's a good one.
很好笑
Oh, my God!
哦，上帝啊！
Shit!
操！
-What the hell was that? -Richard!
- 那是什么？ -理查德！
Richard!
理查德！
-Yeah, I'm here! -Get over here.
- 我在这！ -过来这里
Where's Brad and the lady?
布莱德和那女士在哪里？
-Brad! -Are you okay?
- 布莱德！ -你还好吧？
-Yeah, I'm fine. What's going on? -Brad!
- 是的，我很好。事情怎么样？ -布莱德！
Hey, dickhead!
嘿，混蛋！
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
哦，上帝！哦，上帝！
-Dad? -What?
- 爸爸？ -什么事？
-They got Brad. -What are you talking about?
-他们抓住了布莱德 -你在说什么啊？
-I saw Brad in a car! We gotta go. -What car?
- 我看到布莱德在一辆车里！我们得走了 -什么车？
We've gotta go!
我们必须走了！
Frank, slow down. You are gonna kill us all.
弗兰克，慢一点 你会要了我们所有人的命
You saw a car driving by and Brad was in the back of it?
你看到一辆车开过去 布莱德在后座上？
-Yes. -I don't get that! Why...
-是的 -我没看到！为什么...
I saw him. They were hurting him. You have to stop them!
我看到他了。他们正在伤害他 你必须让他们停下！
-Okay! Where the hell did they go? -Maybe they took a side road.
- 好吧！他们他妈的去哪了？ -也许他们走的是小路
Did you see one? Me neither.
你看到有小路吗？ 我没看到
-At least you don't drive like a pussy. -Shut up, asshole!
- 至少你不要象个娘们一样开车 -闭嘴，混蛋
-What's going on? -Why did you stop?
- 怎么了？ -你为什么停下？
Laura, give me the flashlight, please.
劳拉，给我手电筒
Where's he going?
他去哪里？
-Why did he stop? -Just a minute.
- 他为什么停下？ -就一小会
Stay back. Stay back!
退后，退后
Don't come over here, for God's sake.
别过来，看在上帝的份上
-Fuck me! -Oh, God!
- 操！ -哦，上帝啊！
Richard, get your sister back in the car now.
理查德，带你妹妹回车上
My baby. Do you have her?
我的宝贝 弄好她了？
Jesus Christ...
上帝...
What is he doing?
他在做什么？
He's trying to get Brad's phone.
他要布莱德的电话
-With a stick? -You got a better idea?
- 用棍子？ - 你有更好的主意？
I can't believe I'm gonna do this. Look out.
不敢相信我会做这个 小心
Oh, God...
哦，上帝...
Good boy, Richard.
做的好，理查德
Give it to me.
给我
And drop that. That thing is dirty.
把那丢了 太脏了
You got a signal?
有信号吗？
Thank God. We can call the police and they will tell us what to do.
谢天谢地。我们可以打电话给警察 他们会告诉我们怎么做
-Okay. -Now.
- 好的 - 现在
Please, somebody help me. Please!
拜托，帮帮我，拜托！
God! I can't feel my legs.
上帝！我感觉不到我的腿了
I can't feel my legs!
我感觉不到我的腿了
-Help me! My baby is bleeding! -Who is this?
- 救命啊！我的孩子正在流血 - 你是谁？
Baby! Wake up!
宝贝！醒醒！
-Anybody, please help us. -Oh, Jesus!
- 帮帮我们 - 哦，上帝！
Somebody, please, help us.
无论谁，拜托，帮帮我们
Frank, we gotta get out of here.
弗兰克，我们得离开这里
-Did you get the police? -The phone, it was broken.
- 联系到警察了吗？ - 电话坏了
-Shit. -Please, let's go.
- 操 - 我们走吧
We can't leave him here like this.
我们不能就这样把他留在这
Richard, drag his body off to the side of the road.
理查德，把他扔在路边
Jesus, what do I look like? Your fucking janitor?
上帝，我是什么人？ 你的看家狗？
Thank God. Oh, Marion.
感谢上帝。哦，玛丽恩
Are you all right? You're gonna be okay.
你还好吧？ 你会好的
Marion. Marion?
玛丽恩。玛丽恩？
Marion? Wake up.
玛丽恩？醒一醒。
Wake up. Come on, wake up. Wake up! Wake up!
醒一醒，拜托，醒一醒， 醒一醒！醒一醒！
Laura! Stop!
劳拉！住手！
Stop it!
住手！
Can't you see she's in shock?
你没看到她吓坏了吗？
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起，对不起
Dad, that guy...
爸爸，那个人...
or whoever did that...
无论谁做的
...must've used an axe or a chainsaw. -lt was the work of one sick psycho.
...一定是用的斧子或是链锯 - 一定是神经病干的
-Let's get the hell out of here. -Wait. What about that woman?
- 我们赶快离开这吧 - 等等，那个女人怎么办？
Maybe she got away.
也许她已经离开了
-Maybe the psycho got her. -So, you wanna go after him?
- 也许神经病抓住她了 - 那么，你要追他？
Richard, get in. We're going to the police.
理查德，进来 我们去找警察
-Why don't we go back to lnterstate? -Your mother lives by the sheriff's.
- 我们为什么不回到大路上去？ - 你妈妈住在警长家旁边
We'll be there in 1 5 minutes.
我们15分钟就能到那
Marcott? Never heard of it.
马科特？从没听过
Richard, check the map.
理查德，查查地图
Marcott...
马科特...
Gimme a second.
给我点时间
-There's no Marcott on this map. -Just give it to me.
- 地图上没有马科特 - 给我吧
-I don't see it either. -Maybe that's because it's not there!
- 我也没看到 - 也许就不在那里！
-Laura, give me the local map. -I didn't bring it.
- 劳拉，给我本地地图 - 我没带
-You didn't bring it? -We never needed it before.
- 你没带？ - 我们以前从没用过
-I asked you to. Remember? -I had a lot of things to take care of.
- 我让你带上的，记得吗？ - 我还有一大堆事情得记住
-The presents and... -Who gives a fuck about presents?
- 礼物还有... - 谁他妈的在乎礼物？
Would you please watch your language?
注意你的用词
I'm sorry, but how was I supposed to know you're gonna take a shortcut?
对不起。 但我怎么能想到你会抄捷径？
And how was I supposed to know that you were going to forget the map?
我怎么能想到你会忘带地图？
We've been coming here for 20 years, and you'd never taken a shortcut.
我们来这里20年了 你从没抄过捷径
I'll bring a globe in case you feel like driving by way of the North Pole!
如果你去北极 我会记得给你带个地球仪的
Is there any coffee left?
还有咖啡吗？
A little.
还剩一点
Okay. Pour me some. Let's go to Marcott, then.
好的，给我倒点 我们去马科特
Is anybody else a bit freaked out we are the only car in the road now?
有人觉得 我们是这路上唯一的车子吗？
It's Christmas Eve.
今天是圣诞节前夜
Yeah. Okay. How long have we been driving?
是的，我们开了多久了
It's 7:30.
7:30了
You said it was 7:30 when we took that lady into the car.
我们让那女人上车时 你就说7:30了
That damn thing is broken. All right. Who's got a watch?
该死的表坏了 谁有手表？
-I have a watch. It stopped at 7:30. -Come on.
- 我有，停在7:30了 - 拜托
Don't you guys think that this is just a little wacked?
你们不觉得有点怪吗？
I know you guys think I'm retarded or whatever...
我知道你们觉得我有点蠢或者什么...
but I have a theory and I want you to hear me out, okay?
但我有种看法 我想你们听我说，好吗？
Brad is dead. His body is mutilated and God knows how it got that way.
布莱德死了。尸体被分解了 没人知道是怎么弄得
We are the only people out here and all the clocks have stopped at 7:30.
我们是这里唯一的人 所有的表都停在7:30
This reeks of alien activity, you guys.
外星人干的
-Blow me. -What?
- 去你妈的 - 什么？
Nothing.
没什么
Laura...
劳拉...
can you make her stop that, please?
能让她别说了吗，拜托？
-Let her. Maybe it will help. -It's getting on my nerves.
- 随她吧，也许有用 - 这会刺激我
I can't believe I fell asleep.
不敢相信我睡着了
-How long was I out? -I don't know. Maybe 1 0 minutes.
- 我睡着多久了？ - 不知道。大概10分钟
Are we still on that same road?
我们还在同样的路上？
-Still no Marcott? -No. No Marcott.
- 还是没有马科特？ - 没有，没有马科特
-I don't understand. Did we pass it? -No, I haven't seen anything.
- 我不明白，我们开过头了？ - 没有，我什么都没看到
No lights, no signs, no nothing.
没有灯，没有标符，什么都没有
Shit! What is that?
操！那是什么？
-It's a baby carriage. -I can see it's a baby carriage.
- 婴儿车 - 我知道是婴儿车
-Okay. I'll get out and I'll go see. -No. Don't.
- 好吧，我出去看看 - 不，不要
-Why? -Just get going. I don't like this.
- 为什么？ - 走吧，我不喜欢这样
-Richard, come back here! Richard! -Stop yelling in my ear!
- 理查德，回来！理查德！ - 不要对我大喊大叫！
Richard, come back here!
理查德，回来！
Hey, little guy!
嘿，小家伙
Richard! Frank, no!
理查德！弗兰克，不要！
-You guys suck! -I'm gonna kill that kid.
- 你们这些混蛋！ - 我要杀了那孩子
Oh, God!
哦，上帝啊！
-What the hell was that? -Man, that was good!
- 那是什么？ - 那很好笑
-This is so not funny, Richard! -It's a baby carriage. Why fear?
- 这并不好笑，理查德！ - 婴儿车。有什么怕的？
-It's empty. -No shit!
- 空的 - 操
-That is so not funny! -Nice job. That was dumb.
- 那并不好笑！ - 干的好，无话可说
What is it now?
是什么？
I can't stop thinking about Diane. How are we gonna tell her about Brad?
我想黛安 我们怎么告诉她布莱德的事？
-He was our responsibility. -I don't wanna worry about that now!
- 是我们的责任 - 我现在不想担心那些！
I just wanna figure out some goddamn way to get out of here.
我就想找到路离开这里
I'm sorry.
对不起
Talk about a merry fucking Christmas.
谈谈该死的圣诞节吧
You are not gonna open that. That's my Uncle Herb's present.
你不能打开 那是给荷伯叔叔的礼物
I need this a whole hell of a lot more than your Uncle Herb right now.
我现在比你荷伯叔叔更需要这个
Let's face it. We are lost, Frank. This road is not going to Mom's.
面对现实吧，我们迷路了，弗兰克 这条路不到妈妈家
Let's turn around. We should turn around, Frank.
掉头吧 我们应该掉头，弗兰克
We just passed a sign. Marcott can't be too far.
我们刚刚经过一个标记 马科特不可能这么远
Hey, Sis.
嘿，姐姐
Mom... Mom and Dad are kinda going off the deep end, huh?
妈妈...妈妈和爸爸有点麻烦
They are really losing it.
他们确实迷路了
This whole thing is pretty fucking crazy, huh?
疯狂极了，哈？
Mare?
母驴？
Come on, you've gotta snap out of it, okay? You have to.
拜托，你得醒过来，好吗？ 你得好过来
We need you back here.
我们需要你回来
I... I need you.
我...我需要你
Mom is always going on about what a great shrink you are, so...
妈妈总是说你怎么聪明，那么...
you are the only person that can figure a way out of this. Damn it!
你是唯一一个可以指出一条明路来的人 该死！
Do you remember when your hamster disappeared...
还记得你失踪的宠物鼠吗？
and I told you it had been abducted by aliens?
我告诉你是被外星人绑架了
Well, I lied. Okay? It was me.
恩，我说谎了 是我干的
Me and Kevin. We stuck it in the microwave and we fried it.
我和凯文。我们把它塞到 微波炉里烤了
Marion?
玛丽恩？
Dad!
爸爸！
Dad, it's here again.
爸爸，它又回来了
Richard, I am fed up with your stupid jokes.
理查德，我烦透了你的愚蠢玩笑
-lt wasn't me this time. I swear. -Richard, we do not have time...
- 这次不是我，我发誓 - 理查德，我们没有时间...
Christ! I'm telling you the truth, your fucking assholes!
上帝！我在告诉你事实 你他妈的！
Frank, would you say something for once?
弗兰克，你再说一次试试
-I think we'd better get out of here. -Get going.
- 我想我们最好离开这里 - 走吧
We should have passed a town or a gas station or...
我们应该会经过一个城镇 或是加油站，或者...
a motel, or a crossroads, a junction, something by now!
旅店，十字路，交叉路口或是什么
I know. I know. Just calm down, Laura.
我明白，我明白 冷静下来，劳拉
It's probably one of those closed roads that forest rangers use.
这可能是已经关闭的公路，护林员用的
God! I just feel like we've been driving forever.
上帝！我觉得我们会永远开下去
What is this forest? Is this like the Amazon?
这森林是什么？ 亚马逊雨林？
Last year, I had to drive to Lakewood to talk with a client and I went...
去年，我开车去湖木市 和一个客户谈生意
...on a very roundabout way. -What you seem to do sometimes.
走的是一条非常迂回的路 - 有的时候你会这么做.
I was driving and driving until I had to turn back to the road I came from.
我开啊开啊 直到我不得不回到我来的路上
-What are you talking about? -Some of these roads are designed...
- 你在说什么？ - 有些路的设计...
by engineers who weren't qualified to build a goddamn bird house!
出自还没有资格盖个鸟窝的工程师！
-So? -So? That's that!
- 那么？ - 那么？这就是一条
That's that...
这就是...
Lakewood? Isn't there where Sally Schmidt bought her cottage?
湖木市？ 莎莉施密特买别墅的地方？
Yeah, I think so.
是的，我想是的
Jesus Christ!
上帝！
-What was that? -Some kind of a radio talk show.
- 那是什么？ - 某个电台谈话节目
-That was no talk show. -A public radio, or something.
- 没有谈话节目 - 公众电台或是什么
Public radio? Right.
公众电台？对
-No! Damn it! -You just said it was public radio!
- 不！该死！ - 你说了是公众电台！
I don't know what it was! I don't wanna know what it was!
我不知道是什么！ 我也不想知道是什么！
I just wanna get to the police before anything else goes wrong.
我只想事情变糟之前到警察那去
And I thought last year's Christmas was bad.
我想去年圣诞节很糟
And what was wrong with last year's Christmas?
去年圣诞节怎么了？
-Let's see... Everything? -I thought last year was great!
- 所有的都很糟 - 我觉得去年很棒
-We took the lnterstate! -I was talking about Christmas dinner.
- 我们走的大路！ - 我说的是圣诞大餐
And what's wrong with my family's Christmas dinners?
我家的圣诞大餐怎么了？
Your family.
你家
Your mother always felt you deserved more than a used car salesman.
你妈总觉得你该比一个汽车销售员 得到更多东西
Now that salesman has become a respected sales manager.
现在销售员已经变成了受人尊敬的销售经理
So, I'm sorry, baby, but screw your mother!
那么，对不起，宝贝 但是去你妈的！
-Anything else? -Your damn brother is a freak too!
- 还有什么？ - 你那该死的哥哥也是个变态
He jerks off to gun magazines!
他迷恋枪械杂志
That is disgusting! That is disgusting and that is not fair!
真恶心！太恶心了 那不公平
-Mikey has had a lot of hard times! -Poor little Mikey! Poor Mikey!
- 米其过了很长时间苦日子 -穷米其！穷米其！
Wht do I have to suffer every time I talk to the son of a bitch?
为什么每次和这婊子说话 都这么难受？
-You are just so sensitive! -I know it's Christmas, Laura.
- 你只是太多愁善感了！ - 我知道今天是圣诞节，劳拉
I know it's the season of giving, but I don't give a shit right now!
我明白现在应该施舍 但我现在不在乎
I just wanna get off this goddamn road!
我就想马上从这该死的公路出去！
-Jesus! Mother of..! Fuck! -Oh, Frank!
- 上帝！操！ - 哦，弗兰克
It's okay, honey. We just had a blow-out.
没事，宝贝 我们的轮胎爆了
-Okay. -I'm pregnant.
- 好吧 - 我怀孕了
Marion!
玛丽恩！
Jesus Christ!
上帝！
I smoke pot.
我吸大麻
I'm gonna go change the tire.
我要换轮胎
You handle that wrench like a whore handles a baby.
你拿着扳手就像个 妓女抱着个孩子
-Fucking do it yourself, man. -You watch your mouth, goddamn it.
- 去你妈的，混蛋 - 注意你的话，该死
-All right. -You want some help?
- 好吧 - 需要帮忙吗？
How is Marion doing?
玛丽恩怎么样？
She's pregnant.
她怀孕了
-How are you? -Frankly, it's been much for one night.
- 你好吗？ - 坦白说，一晚上发生太多事了
I'll say.
我会说
-Where did Richard go? -He's probably off smoking a joint.
- 理查德去哪了？ - 可能去吸点大麻
That is not funny! Our son is doing drugs!
那不好笑！ 我们的儿子在吸毒！
Please, Laura.
拜托，劳拉
-Can't you see this is a cry for help? -Christ! It's just a joint, all right?
- 你不明白这是呼救？ - 上帝！只是大麻，行吗？
-Not worse than those pills you take. -My pills are legal!
- 没什么比你拿的药更糟的了 - 我的药是合法的
Pregnant.
怀孕
Man, I hope it's a boy. What's up, little critter?
我希望是个男孩 你好吗，小杂种？
I'm your Uncle Dick.
我是你的老二叔叔
That means you'd better show me some respect, huh?
你最好对我尊敬点，哈？
Or I will fuck you up.
要不我就干你
Okay.
好吧
Are you okay, honey-bunny?
你还好吧，亲爱的小兔子？
-Don't you ever call me that again. -Okay.
- 不要再那么叫我 - 好吧
-Okay, that's fine. -That's what Brad called me.
- 布莱德那样叫我
Uncle Dick. Right on.
老二叔叔。对极了
Fuck!
操！
I love you.
我爱你
Jesus!
上帝！
Okay. I'm done. Let's go.
好的，我弄好了，我们走吧
Richard, we're going!
理查德，我们要走了！
-It's the car! -Oh, my God...
- 是车子！ - 哦，上帝...
Open the door!
开门！
-Open the door! Open the door! -Laura! Laura!
- 打开门！开门！ - 劳拉！劳拉！
Let's go back and get the car!
我们回去追那车
Dad! Dad!
爸爸！爸爸！
Richard! Richard!
理查德！理查德！
Come here! Laura, get in the car now!
过来！ 劳拉，上车来！
-Frank... -Get in, we'll get him!
- 弗兰克... - 进来，我们会追上他！
-Faster! -lt doesn't go any faster, Laura!
- 快点！ - 不能再快了，劳拉！
-Where is he? -I don't know. I can't see him.
- 他在哪？ - 我不知道，我看不到
The son of a bitch shut off his lights!
婊子养的 关灯！
-They are gonna kill him. -No!
- 他们会杀了他！ - 不！
-They are gonna kill him! -No, they won't!
- 不，他们不会
-Yes, they are! -Calm down, mom!
- 他们会！ - 冷静，妈妈！
He'll be all right! I'll get him!
他会没事的！ 我会追到他的！
-lt was Richard! -Shut up! Damn it!
- 是理查德！ - 闭嘴！该死！
It was Richard!
是理查德！
Stop the car! Stop the car!
拦住那车！拦住那车！
Please...
拜托...
My baby!
我的孩子！
What did they do to you?
他们对你做了什么？
-Mom... -Come on.
- 妈妈... - 过来
Come on, baby. You can wake up. Come one, baby.
过来，孩子，你要醒过来 过来，孩子
Laura...
劳拉...
-Laura... -What? What?
- 劳拉... - 什么？什么？
-Mom, he is... -No! No, no...
- 妈妈，他... - 不！不，不...
This is one of his jokes, isn't it? You're just like your father.
这是他开的玩笑，不是吗？ 你就象你爸爸
Remember the time that he took me to New Orleans?
还记得他带我去新奥尔良？
-We never went to New Orleans. -'Course not. You're not his father.
- 我们从没去过新奥尔良 - 当然没有，你不是他爸爸
-What? -Richard is not your son.
- 什么？ - 理查德不是你儿子
-Mom, what are you talking about? -She's out of her fucking mind.
- 妈妈，你在说什么？ - 她疯了
I am not out of my mind. Don't you remember Alan Rickson?
我没疯 你不记得阿伦理克森？
-Laura... -What? What?
- 劳拉... - 什么？什么？
-What did you say? -You remember Alan Rickson?
- 你说什么？ - 你还记得阿伦理克森？
My baby. I don't wanna go. I don't wanna go.
我的孩子，我不想走 我不想走
-Please, let me stay with him. -Come on.
- 拜托，让我和他在一起 - 过来
Let me stay...
让我留下...
Don't take me from him! Oh, God! Please, I don't wanna go.
别让我走！哦，上帝！ 拜托，我不想走
Please, Frank...
拜托，弗兰克...
-What are we gonna do? -We gotta go to the police.
- 我们做什么？ - 我们得找警察
How are we gonna go to the police? We're in the middle of nowhere.
我们怎么找警察？ 我们无处可去
-Come on. Let's go, honey. -We can't leave him here.
- 过来，我们走吧，亲爱的 - 我们不能把他留在这
No, we won't.
是的，我们不会
He was my son. He goes with us.
他是我儿子 他和我们一起走
What is it?
那是什么？
It's what Uncle Mike wanted for Christmas.
麦克叔叔圣诞节要的
Thank God for the gun freak.
谢谢这个恋枪狂
Isn't Michael coming?
迈克尔来了吗？
-Michael? Who the hell is Michael? -It's Richard.
- 迈克尔？谁是迈克尔？ - 理查德
His real name is Michael. Because that is what Alan wanted to call him.
他的真名是迈克尔 阿伦想这么叫他
-Richard is dead! -Okay.
- 理查德死了！ - 好吧
Would you like some pie?
想吃点派吗？
-lt was that sign again. -How far is this fucking town?
- 又是那标记 - 这该死的镇子到底有多远？
-We've been driving for 1 00 miles. -What a wonderful Christmas.
- 我们已经开了100里了 - 多妙的圣诞节啊
I wonder if I should save some pie for Michael?
我想知道我是不是该给迈克尔留点派
-Do you think she's gonna recover? -I don't know.
- 你觉得他缓过劲来了吗？ - 我不知道
But she's gonna have to face reality sooner or later.
但她迟早都要面对现实
-What a wonderful Chrismtas. -God only knows how she will react.
- 多妙的圣诞节啊 - 天知道她会如何反应
-Can't be any worse. -lt can be much worse.
- 不能再糟了 - 还可以更糟
Look, I finished the pie.
看，我把派吃完了
-Could I have a pen, please? -What for?
- 给我支笔，行吗？ - 干什么？
-I'm gonna do a drawing. -Good, good. Here, my pen.
- 我要画画 - 好吧，给你我的笔
-You are so beautiful, Marion. -Jesus!
- 你真漂亮，玛丽恩 - 上帝啊！
Let's hope there's a hospital in Marcott.
希望马科特有医院
What if we never reach Marcott? What if she gets us first?
如果我们永远到不了马科特怎么办？ 如果她先抓住我们怎么办？
-Who? -The lady in white.
- 谁？ - 白衣女人
-That woman with the baby? -Yeah, I saw her in the woods...
- 抱孩子的女人？ - 是，我看到她在森林里
...right after Richard disappeared. -You saw her?
就在理查德失踪后 - 你看到她了？
And then I remembered the story my grandfather used to tell me.
然后我记起祖父过去讲给我的故事
Used to creep me out every time I heard it.
每次听到我都毛骨悚然
Look. I made a drawing of Brad. This was his leg that was hanging out.
看，我画了布莱德 这是他掉下来的腿
-It's for you. -Okay, Mom.
- 给你的 - 好的，妈妈
Wipe your face.
擦擦脸
There was this couple that was driving home from a wedding...
有对夫妇开车回家
in Rhode lsland. It was night. It was raining.
在罗德岛 在晚上，下着雨
And they saw a little girl standing by the side of the road.
他们看到一个小女孩站在路边
And she was just wandering back and forth, clutching the school book.
她走来走去，抓着一本课本
They stopped and they let her get into the back seat...
他们停下来让她坐到了后坐上...
and they tried to talk to her, but she must have been in shock.
他们试着和她交谈 但她一定是吓坏了
They were driving on down the road, all of a sudden they heard a scream...
他们沿路一直开 突然他们听到一声尖叫...
coming from the back seat.
来自后坐
They slammed on the brakes, they nearly had an accident.
他们猛踩刹车， 几乎发生车祸
Miraculously, they didn't go over the cliff. They turned to the back seat...
不可思议的是，他们没有冲下悬崖 他们回头一看...
the little girl had vanished.
那小女孩已经失踪了
There was just her school book there, with her name on it.
只留下她的课本 上面有她的名字
Barbara Rose.
芭芭拉 罗斯
And then they remembered:
他们记起：
the entire Rose family had died in a tragic car accident...
整个罗斯家族已经在一次 车祸惨剧中都死了
right at that cliff, five years earlier.
就在那悬崖 五年前
Come on! Dad, what are you saying? That that woman is a ghost?
拜托！爸爸，你在说什么？ 那女人是鬼？
Look! We've got potato chips!
看！我们有马铃薯片
I'll get them open. I didn't know we had them.
我来打开 我不知道我们有
-Do you want some? -Mom, don't eat them so fast.
- 你想吃吗？ - 妈妈，别吃那么快
-You're gonna make yourself sick. -I am not.
- 你会噎住的 - 我不会
Oh, God! We'd better wake up from this nightmare pretty soon.
哦，上帝啊！ 我们最好马上从这噩梦里解脱出来
Do you feel better, Laura?
感觉好点吗，劳拉？
Dad, who's Alan Rickson?
爸爸，阿伦里克森是谁？
I have no idea.
我不知道
-What was Mom talking about? -I never heard of any Alan Rickson.
- 妈妈在说什么？ - 我从没听说过阿伦里克森
She's in shock. She's talking a whole lot of nonsense.
她吓坏了 她在胡言乱语
-Why would she do that? -You tell me.
- 为什么她会那么说？ - 你告诉我吧
Wow! Look what I found!
看我找到什么了！
Mom, put the gun down. It's dangerous.
妈妈，放下枪 很危险
It's not. It's a toy! It's like the one Michael used to have.
不，只是玩具！ 就像迈克尔以前那支
-Laura! -I was just kidding!
- 劳拉！ - 我只是开个玩笑！
Laura, that is a loaded gun. Put it down.
劳拉，那是已经上膛的枪 放下
You are just trying to scare me. I don't wanna play with you anymore.
你在吓唬我 我不想和你玩了
-Bang-bang, you are dead! -Okay.
- 梆，梆，你死了！ - 好的
Okay, sweetheart. You win.
好吧，亲爱的，你赢了
I'm dead.
我死了
-Do something. -Like what?
- 做点事 - 什么？
-You are the shrink. -Student shrink.
- 你是神经科医生 -实习医生
-Marion... -Mom!
- 玛丽恩... - 妈妈！
-Yes, darling. -We'll play something else now.
- 嗯，亲爱的 - 我们玩点别的
Remember when we used to play house?
还记得我们以前玩的赌博游戏？
I don't wanna play that. I wanna play what Michael and I used to.
我不想玩那个 我想玩迈克尔和我以前玩的
Laura, this is not a game! Our son is dead!
劳拉，这不是游戏！ 我们的儿子已经死了！
-No. -Richard is dead!
- 不 - 理查德死了！
Dad!
爸爸！
Holy shit! The bitch shot me in the leg!
妈的！ 婊子打中了我的腿！
-ls he hurt? -Mom, go back to the car.
- 他受伤了？ - 妈妈，回车上去
-It's gonna be all right. -ls he gonna die too?
- 没事的 - 他也要死了吗？
Nobody is gonna die anymore, okay?
没人会死，好了吧？
How does it look, Doc?
看起来如何，大夫？
We'll see.
我们会知道的
-Hold this. Hold this! -All right.
- 拿着这个，拿着这个 - 好的
-I have to get the pellets out. -Okay.
- 我得把小球拿出来 - 好吧
Light on the wound, please.
照着伤口
-Have you done this before? -No, this is my first time.
- 你以前做过吗？ - 没有，这是我第一次
-Shit! -Light on the wound!
- 操！ - 照着伤口！
Right.
对
-Okay, brace yourself. -Why?
- 好了，自己包扎吧 - 为什么？
Brace yourself.
自己包扎
Oh, God!
哦，上帝！
That hurt more than the shot!
这比中枪还疼
Okay, lift your leg up.
好了，抬起腿
All right. All right. You should be all right now.
好的，好的 你应该好了
-Give me the keys. -I'll drive.
- 给我钥匙 - 我来开车
Easy on the bottle there.
喝水小心些
-You know of a better pain killer? -Driving isn't helping any.
- 你知道一种更好的止痛法？ - 开车没有帮助
It helps.
会有用的
I don't understand it.
我不明白
We should have passed a side-road by now.
我们应该经过一条岔路的
Your grandma's place is probably miles behind us.
你祖母家可能就在前面几里
That's it! This must be a military road!
对了！ 这一定是军用公路！
You think so?
你这么认为？
That's why we never see military trucks. Always on roads isolated!
那就是为什么我们永远看不到军用卡车 总是在隔离的路上
Marcott must be a military base. That's why it's not even on the map.
马科特一定是个军事基地 那就是为什么它不在地图上
-I guess so. -Of course! That's it! That's it!
- 我想是的 - 当然！就是这样！就是这样！
Dad?
爸爸？
-Dad! -It's okay, honey.
- 爸爸！ - 没事，宝贝
-I'm here. I'm here. -Thank God! I thought that...
- 我在这，我在这 - 感谢上帝！我以为...
Your leg...
你的腿...
-Are you okay? -That's not so bad.
- 你没事吧？ - 不太糟
I think we finally got some good news. Come here.
我想我们有好消息 过来这里
Look. Earlier, I showed your mother the North Star.
看，刚才我指给你妈妈北极星
It was on our right side. It still is.
它在我们右边 现在还是
That means we've been headed constantly west.
那就是说我们一直在朝西开
So, if we left the lnterstate somewhere around here...
那么，如果我们在这附近离开大路...
and we headed constantly west on this road...
并且一直朝西开
the road must go right straight to the sea.
这条路一定是直通大海
Marcott must be somewhere on the coast. It makes perfect sense.
马科特一定是在海岸上 非常清楚了
It must be a naval base.
一定是个海军基地
Okay, okay. So how long until we get there?
好的，好的 多久我们能到？
We have about half a tank of gas, we covered 1 50 miles on this road.
我们还有半箱油， 这条路已经跑了150里
That leaves us another 40 or 50 miles until we get to the coast.
到海岸应该还有40或50里
We can reach Marcott within an hour, tops.
我们一个小时能到马科特，最多
You're a genius.
你真是个天才
But you know, I'm more than a little concerned about your mother.
但是你知道，我很关心你妈妈
-Mom? -You're awake?
- 妈妈？ - 你醒了？
-I slept like a log. -How are you feeling?
- 我睡得象块木头 - 感觉如何？
I feel... okay... considering...
我觉得...很好... 我在想...
Now we have got...
现在我们必须...
to stick together. We have got to support each other in our grief.
团结在一起 我们得互相支持
Would you like me to drive, darling?
你要我来开车吗，亲爱的？
-We should reach Marcott soon. -Oh, good!
- 我们会很快到马科特 - 哦，太好了！
-You look not very well. -She's okay.
- 你看起来不太好 - 她没事
Frank, you know, you are a wonderful father.
弗兰克，你明白 你是个很好的父亲
And a wonderful husband too.
也是个很好的丈夫
I want you to know that I understand about you and Sally Schmidt.
我想你知道我理解你和莎莉施密特
-What? -I know the whole thing.
- 什么？ - 我知道所有的事
I know how you two used to meet at the Motel 6 on your lunch break.
我知道你们在你午饭的时候 在6号汽车旅馆约会
It's okay. I completely understand. I have never been able to fulfill...
没事，我都理解 我永远不能满足...
your sexual fantasies. And I want to promise you...
你的性幻想 我想对你保证
that when we get out of here, you can do anything you want to me, darling.
我们离开这里后， 你可以对我做任何事情，亲爱的
And I mean anything.
我的意思是任何事情
Anyway, the most important thing...
无论怎样，最重要的是...
is that the three of us come out of this stronger. What do you think?
我们三个从现在的状况里摆脱出来 你怎样想？
-Not much. -Good.
- 很对 - 好的
Now...
现在...
there's something that has been bothering me ever since I woke up.
有些事我醒过来就困扰着我
-What? -Who are these people in the woods?
- 什么？ - 森林里的人是谁？
Honey, slow down. They are waving.
宝贝，慢点，他们在招手
Hi!
嗨！
Oh, my goodness, why do they look so sad?
哦，上帝，为什么他们看起来这么悲伤？
This is Christmas Eve.
今天是圣诞节前夜
Smile!
笑一笑！
They teach you what to do in this kind of situation?
他们教你在这种情况下怎么做了吗？
Not to panic.
不要害怕
Frank, do you really need to suck on that bottle like that?
弗兰克，你真的需要那样吸瓶子吗？
Frank! It's Jeannine! Quick, stop the car!
弗兰克！是简妮！ 快点，停车！
-Who is Jeannine? -She's my friend!
- 简妮是谁？ - 她是我朋友
Who died 20 years ago.
20年前死了
-And what exactly is your point? -She's dead.
- 你什么意思？ - 她死了
-So? -So drop it!
- 那么？ - 那么别提了！
If the dead are alive, maybe we should check out Richard.
死人活了，也许我们该看看理查德
-Are you crazy? -Think he is comfortable back there?
- 你疯了吗？ - 你不想他安全回来？
Mom, if he was alive, don't you think we would here him?
妈妈，如果他活着 你不觉的我们应该会听到？
Your brother was burned alive. How could he talk?
你弟弟活生生被烧死 他怎么说话？
-Shut up, Laura! -Easy, dad.
- 闭嘴，劳拉！ - 放松，爸爸
-Okay. -She's driving me crazy.
- 好的 - 她快把我弄疯了
-Could I go see Jeannine now? -No, you can't!
- 我能现在去看看简妮吗？ - 不，你不能
-Yes, I can.
- 我可以
-No, you...
- 不，你...
I'm gonna go now.
我得走了
Oh, my God! Dad, stop the car!
哦，上帝！爸爸，停车！
-Mom! -Laura! Laura!
- 妈妈！ - 劳拉！劳拉！
-Laura!
- 劳拉！
Mom!
妈妈！
Oh, God! God! Laura!
哦，上帝！上帝！劳拉！
-Where the hell did she go? -Mom?
- 她去哪了？ - 妈妈？
Mom!
妈妈！
-Maybe she ran away. -Oh, Marion...
- 也许她跑开了 - 哦，玛丽恩...
-Maybe she went into the woods. -Marion, I'm going 60!
- 也许她进了森林 - 玛丽恩，我开到了60
-She would have broken her neck! -Then where is she?
- 她会弄折了脖子！ - 她在哪？
Maybe the lady got her.
也许那女人抓住了她
It's the black car.
是那黑车
You son of a bitch. I'm gonna blow that bastard's head off.
婊子养的 我要把那混蛋的头轰下来
-Marion, where's the ammo? -It's here. I hid it from mom.
- 玛丽恩，子弹在哪？ - 在这，我藏起来了
Come on!
过来！
I got him!
我打中了！
-Mom! -Laura.
- 妈妈！ - 劳拉
-Thank God. -Mom, are you all right?
- 感谢上帝 - 妈妈，你还好吧？
I'm okay. My head hurts a little but I'm fine.
我没事，头受了点伤 但我没事
Sweetheart.
亲爱的
Honey, honey. You got something on your...
宝贝，宝贝 有些东西在你...
Oh, my God! Oh, God!
哦，上帝！哦，上帝！
-Something wrong with my hair? -Oh, God!
- 我的头发怎么了？ - 哦，上帝！
Alan!
阿伦！
-Finally! -No! Stop!
- 终于！ - 不！住手！
-Alan! -Stop! Stop!
- 阿伦！ - 住手！住手！
Laura...
劳拉...
-Daddy? -Laura...
- 爸爸？ - 劳拉...
I made the cheerleading squad.
我创办了拉拉队
This is the happiest day of my life.
这是我这辈子最快乐的一天
Laura...
劳拉...
Dad! Dad!
爸爸！爸爸！
Give me that gun! Stop it, dad! Stop it!
给我枪！ 住手，爸爸！住手！
-You bastard! Stop it! -Marion...
- 混蛋！停下！ - 玛丽恩...
I'm gonna have a baby. You can't leave us. You can't leave us.
我会有个孩子 你不能扔下我们，你不能扔下我们
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. -I've already lost my mother...
- 对不起，对不起 - 我已经失去了妈妈...
and my brother and my boyfriend. I don't wanna lose you.
弟弟和我的男朋友 我不想再失去你
-I don't wanna lose you. -She's gonna get us all anyway.
- 我不想失去你 - 她要杀了我们所有人
No. No one is gonna get us, as long as we keep moving.
不，没人抓得住我们 只要我们一直走
Every time we've stopped, someone's gotten killed. We have to keep driving.
每次我们一停下，就有人被杀 我们必须一直开
We are going to Marcott.
我们去马科特
Let's put your mother in the car.
把你妈妈抬进车里
-You got a cigarette? -ln my coat.
- 你有烟吗？ - 在我衣服里
Alan Rickson was a friend of mine, back in Detroit.
阿伦里克森是我的一个朋友 在底特律
You don't have to say anything, Dad.
你不需要说什么，爸爸
Then one day he came to me for some advice.
有一天他来找我要些设备
He said that he was in love with a woman.
他说他爱上了一个女人
Didn't mention her name.
没有提她的名字
He said that she was married and that she loved him too.
他说她已经结婚了 并且她也爱他
And he wanted to know what he should do about it.
他想知道他该怎么办
And I remember what I said to him...
我记得我对他说...
"You only live once, buddy. Go for it.
“你就只活一辈子，兄弟。 去做吧。
Just go. You go and you see her, and if she loves you...
去做吧 如果她爱你...
she will leave her husband and she will go with you."
她就会离开她的丈夫和你在一起”
-I'm sorry, Dad. -Only talked to him once after that.
- 对不起，爸爸 - 之后就和他谈过一次
He said the woman had decided she didn't want to leave her husband.
他说那女人决定不离开她的丈夫
She already had a kid.
她已经有了个孩子
A little girl.
一个小女孩
She didn't want to lose her.
她不想失去她
Last time I ever saw Alan.
上次我看到阿伦
Always wondered why he never kept in touch.
一直不明白为什么 他不再保持联系
Why did you do that?
为什么他会那样？
If you are scared, alcohol will only make it worse.
如果你吓坏了 酒精只会让你更糟
-You think I'm scared? -You don't need to pretend.
- 你认为我吓坏了？ - 你不需要假装
-It's okay. -No, it's not.
- 没事 - 不，有事
Have you looked at the odometer lately?
你看到里程表了吗？
We've driven 60 miles since the last time we checked the map.
看了地图之后 我们已经开了60里了
I know.
我知道
-We should have reached the coast. -I know.
- 我们应该已经到了海岸 - 我知道
Maybe I miscalculated a little bit.
也许我算错了
Maybe.
也许
Maybe the North Star doesn't indicate north.
也许北极星不是指北
Maybe the map maker was drunk. Maybe the moon's made out of cheese.
也许做地图的喝多了 也许月亮是奶酪做的
Who knows? Everything is so fucked up on this goddamn road!
谁知道？ 这条破路上的所有事都糟透了
After all, we don't have to drive to get to Marcott.
总之，我们不需要开车去马科特
-Maybe there's another way out. -Like what, dad? Flying?
- 也许有别的路出去 - 什么，爸爸？飞？
No. Walking.
不，走
Through the woods.
穿过森林
-This is insane. -Agreed. Agreed.
- 这太愚蠢了 - 同意，同意
-You ready? -We should at least wait until sunrise.
- 准备好了？ - 至少我们应该等到天亮
Remember what you said? Every time we stopped, somebody died.
还记得你说过的话？ 每次我们一停下，就有人死
Let's keep moving.
我们一直走
Did you hear that?
听到了吗？
-Of course I heard that. -What is it?
- 当然 - 那是什么？
I don't know. We're in the woods, Dad. It could be anything.
我不知道。我们在森林里，爸爸 那可能是任何东西
A branch falling, a rat or something, maybe a bird.
折断的树枝，老鼠或是什么 也许是一只鸟
Remember what Laura said about all the faces in the forest?
还记得劳拉说的森林里的脸？
Are there any ghosts in the woods tonight?
今晚森林里有鬼？
-Come on, I'm waiting! -Don't...
- 过来，我等着 -不要...
ever, ever do that again. You hear me?
再那么做 听到我说的了吗？
-What is the matter with you? -We shouldn't have left the car.
- 你怎么了？ - 我们不应该离开车子
That's what's the matter with me!
那就是我怎么了！
The more distance we put between us and the road, the better off we'll be.
我们离公路越远越好
Goddamn! Shit!
该死！操！
Shit! Shit!
操！操！
-Are you all right? -Yeah, just dandy.
- 你还好吧？ - 嗯，被划了一下
-What the hell is that? -You found us a fence!
- 这是什么？ - 围栏！
A fence. Good, good.
围栏，好极了，好极了
There must be a farm on the other side. It's not that tight.
另一边一定是农场 不太紧
I'll hold it up. You crawl under. Go on.
我抬起来 你爬过去
-Now you hold it for me. -Okay.
- 现在你帮我抬着 - 好的
Dad! Look!
爸爸！看！
-Hello!
- 你好！
Hello!
你好！
We're here! We're here!
我们在这！我们在这！
No!
不！
No, it can't be!
不，不可能
How can it be? How can...
怎么会这样？怎么会...
How can it be?
怎么会这样？
-Maybe we got lost. -lf we were lost...
- 也许我们迷路了 - 如果我们迷路了...
we would have come out at the same side of the road.
我们应该从路的同一边出来
-Somebody is fucking with us. -Calm down.
- 有人在玩我们 - 冷静下来
I don't wanna calm down! I want this shit to stop!
我不想冷静！ 我希望这该死的停下来！
-It's still locked. -So what?
- 还锁着 - 怎么？
So who turned on the lights? Who turned them on?
那谁开了灯？ 谁开的？
Laura?
劳拉？
-I'm not getting back in that car. -Me neither.
- 我没回车里 - 我也没有
What are you writing?
你在写什么？
Things I wanna do when this is over.
这件事完了之后我想做的
So?
那么？
Do you want me to help you?
想我帮你吗？
-What about playing bridge? -How old do you think I am?
- 玩桥牌怎么样？ - 你认为我多大了？
I wanna do something... cool.
我想做些...很酷的事情
I wanna buy an Atari, a computer, a bunch of videogames.
我想买一台雅塔利游戏机，一台电脑 一大堆电子游戏
If you wanna do something cool, then I'd go for the PlayStation.
如果你想酷 我推荐PS
What's that?
那是什么？
Never mind. Atari is cooler anyway.
不用在意 雅塔利更酷
Maybe buy some of those Marilyn Bronson CDs.
也许买些玛莲布朗森的CD
Manson.
曼森
-What did you write? -That's none of your business.
- 你写什么了？ - 不关你的事
Stop!
停下！
-What's going on? -I knew it.
- 怎么了？ - 我认得这里
Somebody is playing with us. That's the same cabin as before.
有人在玩我们 那是一样的小木屋
There's probably 1 00 ranger stations on this road. It can't be the same one.
也许这条路上有100个护林员站 不可能一样
No, it can't be. But it is.
不，不可能，但是确实是
-Oh, shit! Go get the flashlight. -No.
- 哦，操！拿手电筒来 - 不
Go get the flashlight!
去拿手电筒！
Marion?
玛丽恩？
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Stop it! Stop it!
住手！住手！
-There's someone in here! I know it! -Dad, stop it!
- 有人在这里！我知道！ - 爸爸，住手！
We are damned.
我们被诅咒了
Dad, come on.
爸爸，过来
No road goes on forever.
没有路是没有尽头的
Where the fog come from?
雾是从哪来的？
-There's no fog, dad. -No fog?
- 没有雾，爸爸 - 没有雾？
Somebody needs to pay a visit to Dr. Sacks to get her eyes checked.
有人需要付钱给萨克斯大夫来检查眼睛
-Where's the whiskey? -I threw it away, remember?
- 威士忌在哪？ - 我扔了，记得吗？
What?
什么？
You threw away my whiskey? My whiskey? Ungrateful little brat.
你扔了我的威士忌？ 我的威士忌？臭小子
-Dad, calm down. -You think because I'm weak...
- 爸爸，冷静点 - 你以为我虚弱...
...you can start messing with me? -Dad, listen to me.
你就可以糊弄我？ - 爸爸，听我说
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
That'll teach you to think twice before you touch my booze.
这是教你在碰我的酒之前 要考虑两次
Dad, please. Please.
爸爸，拜托，拜托
Shut up! Shut up!
闭嘴！闭嘴！
God damn you!
该死
Marion?
玛丽恩？
Marion? My baby! Oh, God, what did I do?
玛丽恩？我的孩子！ 上帝啊，我做了什么？
What did I do?
我做了什么？
Oh, my baby...
哦，我的孩子...
So, you've come for her, huh?
你是来抓她的，哈？
Well, you'll have to kill me first, you bitch!
你得先杀了我，婊子！
Why us, huh? Why?
为什么是我们，阿？为什么？
What did we ever do to you? All we wanted was a nice Christmas.
我们对你做了什么？ 我们就想要个快乐的圣诞节
Is that too much to ask, to have a nice Christmas?
要求得太多了吗，就要个快乐的圣诞节？
Come on out! Where are you hiding?
出来！ 你藏在哪？
Come on! I'll give you a taste of your own medicine, you bitch!
过来！我要让你尝尝你的方式的滋味 婊子！
I'll send you right straight back...
我要直接把你送回...
Dad? Dad?
爸爸？爸爸？
He is dead.
他死了
-He is dead! -Oh, God!
- 他死了！ - 哦，上帝！
Get started!
启动啊！
Come on. Come on!
拜托，拜托！
Start! Come on!
启动啊！拜托
Let's end it!
结束吧！
Come on!
拜托！
Stop playing with me! Please! Please!
别玩我了，拜托！拜托！
He's not here for you!
他不是来接你的！
Dad!
爸爸！
Don't try to talk. Everything is gonna be okay now.
别说话 一切都好了
-Just try to get some rest, okay? -I'm pregnant.
- 休息吧，好吗？ - 我怀孕了
It's all right, Marion. We know.
没事，玛丽恩 我们知道
Both of you are gonna be fine.
你们两个都很好
-How is she? -Are you a member of the family?
- 她怎么样？ - 你是家庭成员？
No, I'm the one who found them. I reported the accident.
不，我发现的他们 我报告的事故
She was lucky, she was thrown out of the car.
她很幸运，她从车里抛出来了
Been in a coma for a few hours, but she's gonna be fine. A few broken...
昏迷了几小时，但她会好的
...ribs and a concussion. -But the others died.
断了几根肋骨，有点脑震荡 - 但其他人死了
-Do they know what happened? -According to the police...
- 他们知道发生什么了吗？ - 根据警察说的...
father must have fallen asleep and crashed into an oncoming car.
父亲睡着了 撞上了迎面而来的车
-A woman and her baby. -They died too.
- 一个女人和她的孩子 - 她们也死了
Well...
恩...
thank you. Thank you for what you did. Doctor...
谢谢，谢谢你所做的一切
-Marcott. Helen Marcott. -Thank you, Doctor Marcott.
- 马科特，海伦马科特 - 谢谢，马科特大夫
Not again.
不要这样
Shit.
操
Hey!
嘿
-Nice car. -Yeah, I'm a collector.
- 车子很漂亮 - 是啊，我是个收藏家
-Can I give you a lift? -Why not?
- 我带你一程？ - 为什么不哪？
Must have been a messy one. Broken glass everywhere.
一定很糟，到处是碎玻璃
I should be at home stuffing myself today.
今天我本来应该在家大吃特吃的
So should they.
他们也是
Did you drop this?
你扔的？
No, what have you got there?
不，什么东西？